{"_id":{"$oid":"616790414d5f380027198150"},"category":"Star Wars","cardPrompt":"In Star Wars, Han Solo's confrontation with Greedo the Rodian ended spectacularly when Greedo missed a blaster shot at Han, who responded with lethal accuracy.","cardAnswer":"Han shot first, dammit!","ID":"1"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"616792f622888723d74d4d3e"},"category":"Captain Planet","cardPrompt":"In \"Captain Planet\", Gaia gives five special rings to the five chosen planeteers. Four are based on the platonic elements - earth, fire, wind, and water - while the remaining ring, Heart, is little use on its own, but necessary for summoning Captain Planet.","cardAnswer":"The heart ring allows for the use of telepathy and communicating with animals.","ID":"2"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167936c22888723d74d4d3f"},"category":"The Legend of Zelda","cardPrompt":"The unified \"Zelda\" timeline that attempts to link all the Zelda games into one coherent timeline is incredibly convoluted, involving time travel and split timelines. While Nintendo hasn't confirmed any one official timeline, most fans agree that the first game, chronologically, is \"Minish Cap,\" and the timeline splits at \"Ocarina of Time.\"","cardAnswer":"The first game is actually \"Skyward Sword\", not \"Minish Cap\".","ID":"3"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167942222888723d74d4d40"},"category":"Star Trek","cardPrompt":"In \"Star Trek,\" Q is a Q from the planet Q. He and his wife, Q, have a son named q.","cardAnswer":"Q is from \"The Q Continuum\", not the planet Q.","ID":"4"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"616795a322888723d74d4d41"},"category":"Power Rangers","cardPrompt":"Being a Power Ranger might seem like an incomparable honor, but it's actually fairly common for Power Rangers to come and go. In fact, in the original series, \"Mighty Morphin Power Rangers,\" only Kimberly, the pink ranger, and Billy, the blue ranger, appear in every episode from start to finish.","cardAnswer":"Kimberly, the Pink Ranger, was not in every episode.","ID":"5"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167971722888723d74d4d42"},"category":"Game of Thrones","cardPrompt":"Brought to Westeros by the Andals, the Faith of the Seven's adherents worship seven gods: the Crone, Father, Maiden, Mother, Smith, Stranger, and Warrior.","cardAnswer":"The Seven are not seven gods, but seven aspects of the same god.","ID":"6"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"616798ad22888723d74d4d43"},"category":"Board Games","cardPrompt":"The board game Pandemic is one of the most popular cooperative board games ever made. Players must work together against the game itself to cure and completely eradicate four different diseases before any one of them overruns the world.","cardAnswer":"Players do not have to eradicate the diseases; they just have to find the cure.","ID":"7"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167997422888723d74d4d44"},"category":"Evangelion","cardPrompt":"The original Neon Genesis Evangelion is about teenager-piloted giant robots called Evangelion, or Evas, battling monsters known as Angels. With a countdown to the apocalypse serving as the story's backdrop, fans were surprised at the final two episodes, which abstractly explored the protagonist's crippling depression, rather than delivering the much-anticipated final epic battle.","cardAnswer":"Evangelions are not giant robot; they are living beings with cybernetic augmentations.","ID":"8"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167a715b836a2c90a84d761"},"category":"Game of Thrones","cardPrompt":"The Tears of Lys, a deadly poison hailing from the same free city as Varys, has been used throughout the show to kill characters both on-screen, such as Myrcella Lannister, and off-screen, such as Jon Arryn of the Vale, Hand of King Robert.","cardAnswer":"The poison used to kill Myrcella Lannister was \"The Long Farewell\", not Tears of Lys.","ID":"9"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167a7b7b836a2c90a84d762"},"category":"Blade Runner","cardPrompt":"Ridley Scott's 1982 film \"Blade Runner\", an adaptation of the Philip K. Dick novel \"Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?\" tells the story of detective Rick Deckard's hunt for a group of fugitive replicants. While many elements and themes were added to the movie, such as Gaff's origami figures, others were lifted directly from the book, such as several of the Voight-Kampff questions, and Roy Batty's iconic line, \"All those moments will be lost in time... like tears... in rain.\"","cardAnswer":"The \"tears in rain\" line is not from the book.","ID":"10"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167a85eb836a2c90a84d763"},"category":"Dragonball Z","cardPrompt":"Saiyans, a race of alien warriors to whom both Goku and Vegeta belong, are capable of transforming into blonde versions of themselves known as Super Saiyans, but only if they still have their tails, which contain the glands necessary for the transformation.","cardAnswer":"Saiyans need their tails to transform into their Great Ape form, not Super Saiyan.","ID":"11"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167a9c7b836a2c90a84d764"},"category":"Lord of the Rings","cardPrompt":"Though most of Sauron's might as a leader is shown through his powerful magic or his terrifying armies, Sauron did have one servant who acted as his diplomat, herald and emissary, the horrifying wraith known as the Mouth of Sauron.","cardAnswer":"The Mouth of Sauron is not a wraith; he is human.","ID":"12"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167aa67b836a2c90a84d765"},"category":"Star Wars","cardPrompt":"\"Rogue One\", the first Star Wars film with no Jedi as primary characters, follows Jyn Erso and her companions as they deliver the plans for the Death Star to the Rebel Alliance, creating one of the most notable continuity errors in the Star Wars universe, as in the original trilogy the discovery of these plans is credited by Mon Mothma to a group of Bothans, a species known throughout the galaxy as incredible spies.","cardAnswer":"The Bothans were credited as stealing the plans for Death Star II in Return of the Jedi, not the original Death Star.","ID":"13"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167ab9db836a2c90a84d766"},"category":"DC Comics","cardPrompt":"In \"Justice League Unlimited\", Wonder Woman is turned into a pig by the sorceress Circe, prompting Batman and Zatanna to strike a bargain with the Greek enchantress. In order to have Diana transformed back, Batman has to beat Circe in a series of riddles, each themed around a traumatic event in Batman's past.","cardAnswer":"Batman did not have to compete in a test of riddles. He had to sing \"Am I Blue\" in a smoky jazz club.","ID":"14"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167ac1db836a2c90a84d767"},"category":"Harry Potter","cardPrompt":"The Shrieking Shack, the most haunted building in all of Great Britain, is technically located in Hogsmeade, but is only accessible from Hogwarts through a secret tunnel located under the Whomping Willow.","cardAnswer":"The Shrieking Shack is not haunted: people believed it was haunted because Remus Lupin used the house to transform into a werewolf.","ID":"15"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6167ad5db836a2c90a84d768"},"category":"Real Life Skills","cardPrompt":"If you wanted to stop heavy bleeding, your best option is to apply a tourniquet a few inches above the wound and tighten it until the bleeding stops.","cardAnswer":"A tourniquet is not the \"best option\", as tourniquets can cause appendages to atrophy due to blood loss. A tourniquet should be seen as a last resort.","ID":"16"}
